Repr's user growth has been
very significant.  In your opinion, what were
the levers and even the playbook
that allowed you to grow so
much?  I am a technology maximalist,
in the sense that I always try to build
the most powerful experience for our people possible.  And the idea is for
the first couple of weeks after you
launch something you usually get
polarizing feedback, so there's people who
love it, people who hate it, and then over time you
realize that the user base that's
left, they really like the product and
they always want you to do more.  The
playbook I've continued to use
since September 2024 is what can we
do to make people build more things
, to make them more autonomous,
whatever crazy idea a user has in their head
to be able to satisfy them.  In
part, I think it has led us to
be a product that is perhaps a little more
complicated, but much more advanced
than other players on the
market.  It is fine for me.  Usually,
especially investors, but
also Twitter or people who are
on there want to see that there is a winner
who destroys all the others.  Tech
has pretty much never worked like this before, and I
think it's starting to become
clear who the key players in
this space will be.  We are one of them,
I hope we always will be, but
here we are, building our own
path to continue to grow and
expand.  I want to become all vibe
coding.  It's a very clean experience,
as powerful as possible, even if it costs a
little bit more, even if it has a little more
complexity, but it's a
creative platform that allows you to do the
highest level work that I can.
Android is, you want to be the i
basically.  Tak.